## Sergii Borodin, Frontend Developer

I am a focused, responsible, full-of-energy, enthusiastic web developer. I do learn web development for more than two years. During this period, I finished two 10-month-long bootcamps, and now, I'm taking my second internship in a company called NordInsight as an intern Frontend developer. Working on a project, I prefer to take on new kinds of tasks and explore new technology to get broad and up-to-date knowledge. In my free time, I'm glad to volunteer at HYF school to help people who have just started studying programming.



Denmark, Århus +45 53 33 12 65

HTML CS:	S Javascript	React.js	Next.js	TS	Git
EDUCATION					
2022 - 2023	GOIT, Full Stack Developer, online   Curriculum  10-month coding bootcamp. Technologies and tools: ReactJS (classes and hooks), TS, Git, Formik, styled-components, emotion, global state management (Redux and useContext), MongoDB, Trello.				
2021-2022	HackYourFuture, Full Stack Developer, Århus   Curriculum 8-month coding bootcamp. Technologies and tools: HTML, CSS, SASS, MaterialUI, ReactJS(hooks), NodeJS, ExpressJS, MySQL, knex.js, Docker, Jira, Agile Scrum methodology, Storybook, Swagger.				
2006-2011	LNAU - Luhansk, Ukraine   Diploma Process engineering - master degree.				
EXPERIENCE					
2023 - now	Frontend Developer at Nordlnsight (internship), Copenhagen Designing a browser-based implant database(React.js, TS, MongoDB).				
2023	Frontend Developer at UNO econetwork (internship), Århus Building a platform for sustainable actors(React.js, SASS, REST API, Axios, Postman, Jira). Created structure (shared layout pattern), routing, navigation, dumb and smart components, code review.				
2021 - 2022	Maintenance worker at HydraSpecma, Skjern Maintenance worker, safe and secure department.				
2015- 2021	Feeding Technician at Torben Bro, Ådum  Work with machinery and small services - Danish integration program.				
CERTIFICATIONS		,		3	
2022	Umbraco Professional course   Certificate Gives a good grasp on building a website from scratch in Umbraco.				
2017-2020	Lærdansk   Certificate  Learn Danish language. Certified with Prøve Dansk 3 level exam.				
PROJECTS		3			
	CarTale   Cars catalog to rent   (Next.js, React.js, Typescript, Tailwind CSS, Headless UI)   Demo   Source				
	<b>Meal-sharing</b>   The project is designed to let users to share meals with each other   (HTML, CSS, React.js, Material UI, swr, REST API,				

## **LANGUAGES**

English, Danish, Ukrainian, Russian

MySQL, Node.js, express.js, knex.js, Docker) | Demo | Source